https://www.zapco.com/privacy

Privacy Policy  Welcome to ZAPCO's website. ZAPCO collects personal information to provide you with a personalized on-line experience. You may visit this site anonymously, without revealing any personal information. When you need additional information writing to us, ZAPCO will request personal information to provide you with a specific product, service, or information, to better understand and communicate with you and to better improve our goods and services.This information may include your name, shipping address, telephone numbers and e-mail address. Personal information is only collected when necessary to provide a product, service, or information. By providing such information, you are agreeing to allow ZAPCO to use the information provided to complete the communication. The processing of personal data collected from the person concerned or from third parties is for purposes related to: 1. To comply with laws related to civil, tax, accounting regulations; administrative management of the relation; contractual obligations; technical support and technical information about the products you have purchased.
2. These activities may also be provided by persons who cooperate with ZAPCO and to which, therefore, the Company shall notify the data such as:
- Part of the Company supply chain   - Technical consultants and other persons who perform activities on behalf of Company
- Public Authorities or agencies in respect of which the reporting is required by law;
- Auditors and certification agencies;
- Companies that provide computer and data matching, data storage, etc...
3. For commercial and marketing aim, such as information and promotion of products and services, evaluating quality of products / services, market research, interactive business communications, both by ourselves and by our affiliates, commercial partners etc. ..  The ZAPCO website may include links to other websites. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that ZAPCO does not own or control, or to people that ZAPCO does not employ or manage. ZAPCO cannot be held responsible for personal information voluntarily disclosed by you to third parties. Please safeguard your personal information.
